let's look at the answer to a dram
technology quiz which was asking us why
not use a normal transistor and a
capacitor when making dram is it because
trench cell is easier to make this is
not true the trench cell is not easier
to make it requires us to bury something
into the Silicon so this one is actually
incorrect trench cells are more
difficult to make than capacitors
technologically trench cell is more
reliable this is also not true trench
cell lets us make cheaper dram chips it
looks like trench cells are more
difficult to make so the chips will be
more
expensive but remember that the cost of
a chip grows quickly when the area is
increased and decreases quickly when the
area is decreased the trench cell
occupies a lot less area on the chip
than the transistor and the capacitor
normally would so if we want to build a
chip that has the same number of bit
with the trench cell or this way the
trench Cell results in much smaller and
thus way way less expensive chips so
this really is the correct answer